Now in case you were wondering, that video was made using GPT Image 2 and Cdance 2.0.
In this video we're going to be talking about a new feature in top view called Storyboard
that's powered by GPT Image 2 and we're going to see everything that it's capable of,
everything that it's not. By the end I'll tell you what I love about it,
what I don't love about it and if you stick around to the end I'll give you some tips on how to get
better results of GPT Image 2. I'd like to thank the sponsor of today's video Top View. They've
given me access to the Storyboard's feature which is it's going to save you quite a bit of money
when it comes to generating Cdance 2.0 videos and I'll show you why. Now if we go into the storyboards
you'll see that we have a couple of examples here to show us exactly what this is capable of.
So all you have to do is give it an image and a short story doesn't have to be too long. Then the AI
will select the best moments from that story in order to create a compelling final piece.
So we have a couple of different use cases in order to give us an idea of what the prompts
actually need to look like and it doesn't matter the style that you give it because as you can see
here they gave it an anime sort of style for the starting image and they didn't even mention
anime in the story but it just knows it picks up exactly what it looks like and it kept the style
even for the backgrounds looks amazing so as you can see in the final video it really held up to
the original image and the story itself. So with Storyboards it actually gives us the ability to add
16 reference images. So what we're going to do is actually add a couple of reference images to the
story that I want to create now. So I've added my character the character's van and the marauders
that is going to be escaping. So just describe what happens the AI will pick the best moments to draw
from. A futuristic car driver races tunnels and storms pursuing a relentless robotic hunter.
So let's go with something a little bit simple like that. So what we've got is a ranger drives a
hovering van through the desert to escape motorcycle marauders driving through a sandstorm they
can't survive. We've got a little bit of conflict there. It's something a little compelling that
the AI can pull from. So we're going to go 16 by 9. The great thing is that if you're doing
social media you can also do 9 by 16 and we need GPT image 2. We can select either 2k or 4k.
I really wouldn't go with 1k unless you're using the 4 moments selection. I'd go with 9 and just
2k or 4k. In this case we're going to go 4k because I feel like that way we'll get a lot more
information in there. So as you can see to generate the board it's only 1.4 credits so it's not not a
lot at all. So let's generate that. Okay so let's have a look at what we got. So we've got the driver
then we establish a scene. We see the marauders coming in and they start chasing him. Heads
towards the storm which is great. I love the way it just took over the entire sky. Drives in and
they get destroyed and he drives out. It's perfect. It's exactly what we needed. So we have two options
from here. We can either generate the video directly from here which I'll actually start that
process now. And that way we'll see what the difference is between doing it this way or going
into the agent V2 that way we get a little bit more detail in the prompts themselves. So let's
start with this. Generate the video directly as it is. And as you can see it'll send this straight
to cdance 2.0. It'll give us like a basic prompt generator video based on the storyboards in this.
It's basically the same prompt that we gave it before. It gives us 15 seconds and we can actually
choose to cue this into priority mode for instant start. So then that way we can start it straight
away. And by the time we're done with the rest of it this should be done. But what I'm going to do
is I'm actually going to go to agent V2. Now once we're in here we can add all our bits and pieces. So
what we have is this reference image that we've got a storyboard there and we can add some references
as well. So I had the exact same references that I added before. That way we have all the references
to the character, the van, the marauders and everything. So the agent has given me these three
sections which will go for 10 seconds each and we have a wide angle low shot with the van driven
by the ranger speeds across the vast desert plains kicking up a whole bunch of dust and it's been
chased by the marauders. Yeah everything looks pretty cool. And sometimes what's actually a good
idea is to come in here and select what you want from all of these. So I usually go with cinematic
story. You can actually go anime if you do an anime something like that. But I will go with
cinematic story and confirm and then I'll enhance it. That way it'll actually use details like
descriptive details of the actual scene that you wouldn't have thought of otherwise. And that
usually doesn't take too long which is great. The one thing that I will say is before you click generate
make sure to get rid of anything that you don't want. So in my case I don't want a dialogue voice
over. So let's get rid of that. So it does tend to add dialogue or sometimes voice overs so we
don't really need that sort of thing in there while that's generating. And this is what it gave us
for this shot. That look of surprise. Now all in all even though we didn't use Agent V2 for
this specific one for a 15 second shot it actually did really well. I would have liked to see
a little bit more destruction when it comes to the bikers but all in all I think it's actually
pretty amazing what it's able to do. That's so good. I love it. Now the great thing about top view
is that it'll give you access to a whole bunch of AI image and video tools at a rather affordable price
which if you're a filmmaker or content creator that needs to be generated videos consistently
I really think this is the way to go. Be sure to check out the new ultra plan they have. Now the
issue that I've had with CDANCE 2.0 video generating it takes up a lot of credit when it comes to
generating these videos. So unless you have the 365 unlimited plan it tends to eat away your credits
very quickly. In the past I've told everyone that they should definitely check out the business
plan in top view because the price was pretty good but now they have the ultra plan and with
the ultra plan it actually reduces how much the CDANCE generation's cost. It will give you the
365 days of unlimited generations using CDANCE 2.0 and now GBT image too as well but it'll cost
less than it did with the business plan which is great because then when you're not using the
unlimited plan and you're actually wanting to do things much quicker with the priority mode
it's going to cost much less. I think it equates to 10 cents per second. One other thing that I forgot
to speak about in the other videos was concurrent tasks and the great thing about using top views
plans is that you're able to set up more tasks concurrently using the unlimited feature. If you
would get the base ultra you'd be able to set up 12 concurrent tasks which is great because then
that means that you can set up a whole bunch of tasks the night before wake up in the morning
and you'd be ready to go. Now one thing that I have been asking a couple of other videos is
how long does it take for the unlimited and really it varies depending whether it's peak off
peak hours. I've gotten some videos as quickly as two hours and some that have taken up to seven
hours. It just really depends on how much the server's been used at that moment. So what we're
able to do is actually open this up in the image edit and using GBT image too. We can fit our storyboards
and marauders and also our van because we don't need anything else for this specific image and
say edit only image for motorbikes approaching the van from behind and change nothing else.
Then we can generate that. As you can see it changes only image for which is great because then
that way it means that you can go into each individual storyboard and make modifications in order
to actually have more control over the final video. Okay so the issue that we had with agent V2 is that
because we didn't split up the images it replicated the storyboard through each of the videos. So
you can actually see in all three of the 10 second clips it uses images from the entire storyboard.
He's driving into the storm in each one whereas when we go back to the other one 15 second one
that we created just one clip from it aside from the ridiculous expression at the start of it my
shock and horror you'll see that it follows each of the shots perfectly and it worked exactly how
we needed to. Now one of the things that I would probably say to do is to trim each of the images
so they will be independent that way you'd be able to feed each of the shots to agent V2 exactly
what they need to be as opposed to reusing them through the entire thing. That's the only issue
that I had other than that. The idea of being able to use storyboards is actually extremely handy.
Let me know in the comments down below if this is a sort of tool that would really come in handy
with your workflow. I believe in order to save credits and save time I'm going to be using this
quite a bit. So if you like this video don't forget to click like and subscribe to the channel it
really helps boost the channel's visibility and I really appreciate it. If you're interested
in playing around with storyboards you should definitely check out top view there's going to be a
link in the description and if you enjoyed watching this video I think you'll like these two as well.
I'll see you guys next time.